

G. HAMZA CHOUDHURY

(253)-266-5978 | contact@gcteam.dev|Seattle WA.

SUMMARY

Analytical problem solver with 550+ training hours in Web development. Interested in attaining a career in Web development to highlight my previous work experience and complement my leadership and teamwork abilities. I enjoy object-oriented programming and finding innovative ways to execute solutions. With a persistent and growth mindset, I strive to be a full-stack developer in the next 6-12 months.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Node.JS
- MongoDB
- HTML5
- CSS
- Unit Testing with Mocha
- Git
- Phyton
- React
- Bootstrap

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER • DELGADO COMMUNITY COLLEGE-GENERATION USA • 04/2022 -07/2022.

Completed 12 weeks of intense training on developer tools like JavaScript, Git, and Agile project management methodologies.

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER • FREELENCER • 08/2021 - CURRENT.

Provides comprehensive consultation of project objective and scope by utilizing project management, and CMS service for e-commerce websites.

E-COMMERCE DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP • FREEMOTE • 05/2021 -07/2021.

Learned building e-commerce websites with HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, and Shopify liquid.

MEDICAL ASSISTANT • PACMED, WA • 02/2019 -04/2022.

Contributed to patient care with proficient documentation and excellent communication.

SERVER • MASALA RESTAURANT, IL • 02/2013 -01/2017.

Recorded and served high volume customer orders with excellent standards while maintaining inventory as a Lead Server.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

W3 SCHOOL JAVASCRIPT CERTIFICATIONS • 07/2022 • GENERATION USA

ASSOCIATE DEGREE - HEALTH MANAGEMENT. • 12/2021 • PMI INSTITUTE - GPA 3.71

PROGRAMMING FOUNDATION CERTIFICATE • 12/2011 • ICE COLLEGE – BIRMINGHAM, UK.







